[{"id":686,"question":"Which command can be used to write onto other currently logged in user\u2019s console output terminal.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"notify","answer_b":"alert","answer_c":"write","answer_d":"broadcast","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"},{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":681,"question":"Who designed the Linux OS?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Linus Torvalds","answer_b":"Steve Jobs","answer_c":"Steve Wozniak","answer_d":"Steve Linus","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1080,"question":"Which command do we need to use if we want to see all packages installed on the system (Ubuntu)","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"dpkg -l","answer_b":"packageall -l","answer_c":"dpkg -a","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":668,"question":"What will the following command do - $ chmod 888 file","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"It enables r,w,x premissions for all users","answer_b":"It disables r,w,x premissions for all users","answer_c":"It enables r,w,x permissions only for owner of the file","answer_d":"None of the above.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"We can provide the permission values in octal number system and 888 is not a valid octal number.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":665,"question":"Choose the correct usage of \u2018cd\u2019 to move into the parent directory.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"cd","answer_b":"cd ..","answer_c":"cd .","answer_d":"cd\/","answer_e":"None of the above","answer_f":"cd.."},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":739,"question":"How to dump pod logs (stdout) in Kubernetes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl log my-pod","answer_b":"kubectl pod logs my-pod","answer_c":"kubectl logs my-pod","answer_d":"kubectl pods logs my-pod","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":824,"question":"test123","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"test","answer_b":"test2","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Angular"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1081,"question":"Where are the online repositories configured on a Debian\/Ubuntu Machine","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"\/etc\/apt\/sources.list","answer_b":"\/etc\/apt\/yum.repos","answer_c":"\/etc\/fstab","answer_d":"\/etc\/apt\/repos","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":725,"question":"How to list all Kubernetes pods in the current namespace, with more details?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl get pods -o wide","answer_b":"kubectl get pods -f more","answer_c":"kubectl get pods -v","answer_d":"kubectl get pods -o details","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":691,"question":"Which operator can be used to throw a process into background?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"&","answer_b":"&&","answer_c":"|","answer_d":"||","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"}]